어지러운 전국 시대.
It is the turbulent Sengoku period.
카라쿠리인이 사는 지팡구국에서는 군웅할거하여 밤낮으로 접전이 계속되고
Warlords keep on fighting day and night over
Jipangu State, where Karakuri people live.
카라쿠리 무예가들도 승리와 영광을 꿈꾸며 맹렬히 싸우고 있었다.
Karakuri Martial Artists were sharpening their swords, dreaming of victory and honor.
그리고 지금, 카라쿠리 무예가 제일을 꿈꾸는 터무니없는 영웅이 탄생했다!
And now, a wild hero has arrived, seeking to be the number one Karakuri Martial Artist!
무사시 등장이오!
Musashi is here-dasu!
카라쿠리 검호전: 무사시 로드
Karakuri Kengouden
Musashi Road
(The Story of Karakuri Martial Artist: Road of Musashi)
사내는 언제나 세계 한가운데서
A man always dreams of the day
제일 강해질 날을
in the center of the world to become
아! 아! 꿈꿔라
AH! AH! the strongest
마음의 칼을 넓은 하늘로 번쩍 쳐들어
Raise the sword of your heart high to the wide sky
모험의 길의 막을 연다
Raise the curtain to the road of adventure
지팡구국을 떠도는 검호
A skilled swordsman roams on Jipangu State
그 이름은 카라쿠리인 무사시
His name is Musashi, a Karakuri man
격렬한 승부의 소리는
The sound of fierce duels
눈부신 인생
makes life dazzling
싸웠던 어제보다도 오늘 강해진다
Battles of yesterdays make you stronger today
무예! 이도류 무사시
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
내일은 빛난다
Tomorrow will be glorious
격렬한 승부의 소리는
The sound of fierce duels
눈부신 인생
makes life dazzling
싸우는 한껏 고요함과 함께
Fight the utmost with the stillness
무예! 이도류 무사시
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
미간이 반짝였다 무사시!!
His eyes shined! Musashi!
호색한 발명가 겐나이에게 잠수함을 만들어 받은 무사시 일행은 바닷속을 찾아 돌아다녀, 메가톤성을 발견한다.
After making a perverted inventor Gennai make a submarine, Musashi and others search the sea, and found Megaton Castle.
필사적인 각오로 거기에 올라타 날뛰는 무사시 일행.
With a determination, Musashi and others got in to rage.
메가톤성에 손해를 입혔지만, 잠수함도 너덜너덜해지고 말았다.
They damaged Megaton Castle, but also destroyed was their submarine.
큰 웃음거리
문어 춤 작전이오
Big Laughter
Octopus Dance Strategy
잠수함을 수리한 무사시 일행은 노부나가의 본거지를 찾고 있었다.
After repairing the submarine, Musashi and others were looking for Nobunaga's base.
난 뱃멀미해서 상태가 안 좋아.
I don't feel so good. I'm seasick.
겐나이 씨, 뱃멀미할 때는 코 끝을 핥으면 괜찮아지오.
Mr. Gennai, they say seasickness will be gone if you lick your own nose-dasu!
정말이냐?
Yeah, right!
싫어, 무사시! 잘도 이런 것에 날 태우다니. 이대로 부상하지 않으면 어쩔 거냐.
No, Musashi! How dare you get me ride onto this thing!? I don't know what will happen if we don't go up now!
자기가 만든 것 아니오! 더 자신을 가지는 건 어떻소?
You made this-dasu! You should be more confident with what you made-dasu!
내가 만들었으니까 믿을 수 없는 거야!
I can't trust this thing because I made this!
어? 지라이얀!
Huh? Jiraiyan!
어이! 이쪽에는 눈에 띄는 게 없어!
Heya! There's nothing over here!
음, 이 넓은 바닷속의 어딘가에 본거지가 있을 터이지만...
There should be their base somewhere in this wide sea...
어이! 저쪽 찾아 볼게!
Hey! I'll go find over there!
아무래도 좋으니까 서둘러. 어서 땅 위로 올라가.
Just hurry up. Hurry up to the grounds.
겐나이 님. 이 주변 이외에 적의 본거지가 있을 만한 곳이 있습니까?
Mr. Gennai, is there somewhere else than this place where the enemy's base is likely to be at?
그런 걸 알 리가 없잖아. 어쨌든 빨리 지상으로 돌아가.
There's no way for me to know that. Just go back to the grounds!
코지로 님. 이러니저러니 해도 3시간 이상 있었던 것 같으니, 이 주변에서 일단 쉬는 게 좋지 않을까요.
Mr. Kojirō. We've been underwater more than 3 hours. Maybe it's best for us to take a rest around here.
찬성.
Agreed.
그렇네요. 여기서 안달해도 바다는 넓으니 말이지요.
You're right. Even if we hurry, the sea is too wide.
잠깐 기다리시오!
Just a moment-dasu!
무슨 일입니까, 무사시 님?
What's wrong, Mr. Musashi?
저건 뭣이오?
What's that-dasu?
-코지로 님.
-예.
-Mr. Kojirō.
-Roger.
이, 이건!
L- look!
이것이야말로 노부나가의 본거지임에 틀림이 없습니다.
This must be Nobunaga's hideout.
드디어 발견했소!
We finally found it-dasu!
그래도, 잘도 이렇게 큰 요새를!
But still, how did they built a base this big here?
노부나가라는 자, 한계를 알 수 없는 힘을 가진 자이군요.
That Nobunaga guy must be having a power that we do not know about.
거대한 요새가 뭐 어떻단 것이오! 어차피 소심한 자의 요새. 인간 최후의 승부는 배짱의 거대함에 달려 있소!
Their base is big, but so what-dasu? It's a base of a coward-dasu. The victory depends on big guts-dasu!
-오?
-역시 무사시 님. 잘 말씀하셨습니다.
-Oh?
-Good job, Mr. Musashi. Well said.
어뢰이오!
Torpedo-dasu!
으아! 배에 구멍이 뚫렸소!
There are holes in the ship-dasu!
다시 옵니다!
Incoming again!
여긴 일단 퇴각합시다.
Let's retreat for now.
난 사내다, 지라이얀!
Jiraiyan! I'm the man!
두꺼비 기름은 케로키치고~
Kerokichi's the toad oil~
어이! 그쪽에서 뭐 찾았냐!
Hey! Did you find something over there?
앞을 보라고?
Look at front?
착탄 확인. 최저 2발은 명중했습니다.
Impact confirmed. At least 2 were hit.
아무리 이 바벨 13을 발견했다고 해도 할 수 있는 것도 없을 터.
They found out Babel 13 at last, but it's not going to help them.
한조. 방심하면 안 된다.
Hanzo. Do not treat this incident lightly.
노부나가 님.
Lord Nobunaga.
놈들에 관한 일이다. 여길 발견한 이상 분명 침입을 재촉할 게 틀림없다.
It's about them. Since they found out this place, they will try to invade.
알겠냐, 너희들도! 지금 이상으로 경비를 엄중하게 해서 살려 돌려보내면 안 된다.
That goes for you too. Make the guards more strict and never let anyone go back alive.
예!
Yessir!
젠장... 기껏 적의 기지를 찾았는데...
Damn... We finally found the enemy's base, and...
다시 가게 되면 가만은 안 두오!
If I ever go there again, I will finish them-dasu!
그래도 잠수함은 이제 못 써.
But you can't use the submarine anymore.
에, 그럼 더는 거기에 갈 수 없게 되오?
Does that mean we can't go there anymore-dasu?
다시 한번 정도 수리하면 어떻게 안 되오?
Can't you just try repairing it once again-dasu?
이 꼴을 봐라. 이건 이제 너덜너덜해.
Look at this. It's unusable.
아무리 다시 간다고 해도, 그만큼의 경비를 돌파하는 건 무리입니다.
Even if we can go again, it's difficult to go through that security.
그럼 우린 이대로 손발도 꼼짝 못하고 있는 거야?
Then, will we be unable to do anything at all anymore?
다른 방법을 생각해내야만 합니다.
We have to think of something else.
코지로 님, 무언가?
Mr. Kojirō, do you have any idea?
예. 저 깊은 바닷속에서 놈들이 살아가는 건 어디선가 공기를 집어들이지 않으면 불가능합니다.
Yes. For them to live in that deep sea, they have to take air from somewhere.
그래, 그거야! 이 주변 어느 섬에 통풍구가 있단 거네!
I see! That's it! You're saying that there's a ventilation on some island around here!
뭣이오, 그게?
What's that-dasu?
어쨌든 공기구를 찾아낼 수 있다면 분명 그 기지 속에 쳐들어갈 수 있을 터.
Anyway, if we can discover where their ventilation is, we should be able to get into their base.
-어이, 어이!
-어?
-Hey, hey!
-Huh?
오츠루도 그런 곳에 있지만 말고 등이라도 태우면 어때?
Otsuru, you should tan your back, instead of doing nothing over there!
역시 나, 따라가는게 좋았을 지도...
Maybe I really should have followed them...
냅둬. 어차피 각다귀에게 물리는 것 말고는 아무것도 못 찾을 테니.
Leave them be. They won't find anything, else than being bit by mosquitoes.
그래도 무사시 씨, 단체 행동 못하는 사람이니까...
But Mr. Musashi can't do collective actions...
덥소, 이 섬... 마치 남쪽 섬에 간 느낌이오. 그렇지 않소, 코지로?
This island is hot-dasu... It's like we're on a southern island-dasu. Don't you agree, Kojirō?
뭐냐, 코지로. 힘드냐?
What is it, Musashi? Are you tired already?
아니, 그런 게 아니오. 나, 목이 말라서 바짝 말라버릴 것 같소.
No, that's not it-dasu. I'm so thirsty that I might become stale-dasu.
우와! 바나나이오!
Yay! Bananas-dasu!
이렇게나 잔뜩 있다니 기쁘오!
I'm happy that there are a lot of them-dasu!
음, 무사시 님은 대단하군요. 원숭이가 울며 달아날 정도의 나무 오르는 실력.
Mr. Musashi is really skillful. That tree-climbing skill will even scare a monkey away.
이건 맛있소. 나 하나라도 좋으니까 바나나를 배 가득히 차도록 먹어보고 싶었소.
This is delicious-dasu! I always wanted to eat at least one banana that'll make my stomach full-dasu!
어이, 무사시! 풀 먹고 있을 때가 아니잖아?
Hey, Musashi! It's not a time to be eating some grasses!
풀이 아니라 바나나이오!
It's banana, not grass-dasu!
우린 먼저 가자.
Let's go first.
왜 그러냐! 바나나라도 목에 걸렸냐?
What's wrong? Did a banana stuck in your neck?
저기에 큰 토관이 있소!
A large earthen pipe is over there-dasu!
뭐라!?
What!?
저기이오!
That-dasu!
코지로 님.
Mr. Kojirō.
가 봅시다.
Let's go.
시원하오!
How refreshing-dasu!
무사시, 경주하자.
Musashi, let's have a race!
어이! 너희들! 어디에 적이 숨어 있는지 몰라!
Hey, you guys! We don't know where are the enemis hiding at!
그러니까 어서 강을 건너려고 하고 있는 것이오! 그렇지 않소, 지라이얀?
That's why we're trying to go over the river-dasu! Right, Jiraiyan?
그래그래! 누가 먼저 건너편 바위에 닿는지야! 가자!
Right, right! We'll see who'll reach the rock on the other side first. Let's go!
수영하고 있긴 한 거야, 쟤들?
Are they even swimming or what?
분명 무사시 님의 수영은 코지로 님께서 배웠을 터.
I heard that Mr. Musashi learned swimming from you, Mr. Kojirō.
이야, 정말 거대한 토관이오!
What a giant earthen pipe-dasu!
이것이야말로 적의 아지트의 통풍구야.
This must be the ventilation of the enemy's hideout.
그럼 어서 들어가자!
Then, let's get in right away!
잠깐!
Wait!
기다려라, 기다림 콜이다!
Wait! This is a wait call!
여기서 바벨 13에는 이 켄신이 못 가게 할 것이다!
I, Kenshin, will not let you go to Babel 13 from here!
무슨! 이 신겐 님이 너희들을 저 세상에 보내 주겠다!
No way! I, Shingen, will send you guys to hell instead!
이런 곳까지 엄중하게 경비하고 있었구나...
They're guarding a place like this too...
네놈들의 잔꾀 따위는 전부 꿰뚫고 있다. 다들 해치워라!
We already know all your shallow plots. Everyone, get them!
에잇, 거추장스럽소! 다들 한꺼번에 해치워 주겠소!
You're being pain in a butt-dasu! I'm going to get rid of all of you-dasu!
네이놈, 건방지다!
How impudent of you!
신겐! 여긴 바로 힘을 모으자!
Shingen! Let's combine our powers right away!
좋다! 여기서 당하면 우리가 노부나가 님에게 죽을 테니!
Agreed! Lord Nobunaga will kill us if we let them go through!
천지합체!
Sky Ground Fusion!
아, 안 되오!
T- this is bad-dasu!
자, 어디서든 덤벼들어 보아라!
Come attack whenever you're ready!
없어.
They aren't there...
저 놈들하고 싸우면 힘드오. 오늘은 패스하오.
Fighting them is tiresome-dasu. We'll skip this for now-dasu.
그렇지.
You're right.
과연 무사시 일행은 잠입해 내는가? 질풍노도의 후반을 기다려라!
Will Musashi and others make their way in? Wait for the stormy latter half!
카라쿠리 검호전 무사시 로드
Karakuri Kengouden: Musashi Road
아, 꽤나 땀흘리고 말았소.
We sweated a lot-dasu.
정말, 기껏 통풍구를 찾았더니 바로 도망쳐오다니 정말 야무지지 못해.
Running away right after finding the ventilation is really slovenly.
그럼 센짱이 신겐신 해치워 줄 것이오?
Then, Sen-chan, will you get rid of Shingenshin-dasu?
싫어.
No.
자, 자, 싸우고 있을 때가 아닙니다.
Now, now, it's not a time to be fighting.
또 새로운 작전을 생각해야...
We need a new strategy again...
아, 봐봐! 무사시 씨!
Look, Mr. Musashi!
뭔 일이오, 오츠루?
What's up-dasu, Otsuru?
귀여워!
How cute!
정말이오!
True-dasu!
멋지오!
How cool-dasu!
다들 고민하고 있는데 잘도 느긋한 소릴...
Everyone are troubled and they're...
또 뛰었어! 대단해, 돌고래는!
It jumped again! Dolphins are awesome!
나도 돌고래가 되어서 바닷속을 자유롭게 헤엄쳐 다니고 싶소.
I want to become a dolphin so that I can swim freely in the sea-dasu.
그거다!
That's it!
우리도 돌고래가 되자.
We'll become dolphins, too.
이런 걸로 정말 잘 될 것 같소?
Are you serious that this will work-dasu?
그럼 네게 뭐 다른 아이디어 있냐? 말해 봐!
Then, do you have any better idea? Spit it out!
그, 그건 아니오.
I- I don't-dasu...
그럼 궁시렁대지 마!
Then, don't complain!
이런 돌고래돌 고래더냐?
Dolphin tolls fins...
완벽하다. 이걸로 놈들을 속일 수 있겠어.
Perfect. This will be enough to fool them.
어딜 봐서? 이런 서투른 봉제 인형, 곧장 발각되오!
Perfect? A clumsy stuffed toy like this will be revealed soon-dasu!
서툴러서 미안하네! 이래도 우리가 정성들여 꿰맨 거야!
Sorry for being clumsy, duh! We really did our best to make this!
이 딱한 손가락을 봐!
Take a look at these pitiful fingers!
안 될 일을 하니까이오.
It's because you did something you can't-dasu.
시끄러워! 내가 이렇게 열심히 했는데 그래도 너 입고 싶지 않다는 거야?
Shut up! After all my hard work, you still don't want to wear it!?
그래, 무사시 씨! 입어 줘! 난 재봉은 잘 못 해도,
Yeah, Mr. Musashi, wear it! It's not like I'm good at needlework,
세탁, 청소, 요리를 포함한 가사 일체 중 할 줄 아는 게 하나도 없는 센히메 님이 저렇게나 열심히 만든 거야!
but that Senhime, who can't do laundries, cleaning, cooking, and all other housekeeping at all, really did her best to make!
아니, 거기까지 말할 필요까지는...
Hey, you don't have to tell that...
아, 알겠소, 입겠소. 입으면 되오!
I get it, I'll wear-dasu! I'll wear-dasu!
귀엽다!
How cute!
그렇소? 역시!
Do you think so-dasu! I knew it!
자! 준비되면 출발하자!
Let's go, since we're ready!
간다!
Here I go!
영차!
Heave, ho!
무사시 씨!
Mr. Musashi!
알겠어? 코지로 씨가 말하는 거 잘 듣고, 누구도 귀찮게 하면 안 돼.
Listen to Mr. Kojirō well, and try not to bother anybody.
알겠소.
Got it-dasu.
그리고, 어떤 위험한 일이 있을 지 모르니 쥬베 씨 옆에 잘 붙어 있어.
And, since you don't know what kind of danger will be there, be always with Mr. Jube.
알겠소.
Got it-dasu.
아, 그리고, 상어는 조심해. 상어는 문어를 제일 좋아한다고 하니까.
Oh, and, be careful of sharks. Sharks like octopuses.
상어에게도 고래에게도 충분히 조심할 것이오. 그럼 갔다 오오!
I'll be careful of both sharks and whales-dasu. See you later-dasu!
걱정이야, 무사시 씨. 어서 돌아와!
I'm worried about Mr. Musashi so much. Come back soon!
자. 무사시. 해.
Now, Musashi, do it.
정말 해야만 하오? 나 부끄럽소.
Do I really have to do this-dasu? I'm embarrassed-dasu.
더 맛있게 춤추지 못하겠냐!
Dance more tastily!
문어, 문어, 나는 완전 맛있는 문어이오.
문어, 문어, 에도식 초밥으로는 최고이오.
octopus, octopus, I'm a totally tasty octopus-dasu.
octopus, octopus, I'm the best for Edo-Style Sushi-dasu.
어? 어이, 봐봐! 맛있어 보이는 문어가 있어!
Huh? Hey, look! There's a tasty-looking octopus!
어디?
Where?
어, 둥글둥글하고 살쪄서 먹을 맛이 나겠는걸.
Hey, it's round and fat, good enough to eat.
어이, 뭘 할 생각이야?
Hey, what are you up to?
뭐, 잠깐 이 녀석 잡으려는 거야.
I'm just going to catch that.
문어문어~
octopus, octopus~
어때, 맛있어 보이지!
It sure looks tasty!
오, 생기가 있는데, 이 놈!
This guy looks great!
어서 안주로 만들어 먹어 버리자!
Let's eat this as a side dish.
뭐야, 이건? 죽은 거 같은데.
What's this? This isn't right.
이, 이건 직물 아니냐.
I- isn't this cloth!?
뭐야!?
What!?
문어입니다!
I'm an octopus!
가짜다!
A fake!
문어 춤 작전 성공이오!
Octopus dance plan was successful-dasu!
해냈구나!
He did it!
괜찮소?
Are you alright-dasu?
무사시 님의 문어 춤, 훌륭했습니다.
Mr. Musashi, your octopus dance was splendid.
그렇소? 오츠루에게 보여주고 싶었소!
Do you think so-dasu? I wanted to show this to Otsuru-dasu!
자, 발각되지 않을 동안 노부나가가 있는 곳을 찾자.
Now, let's find where Nobunaga is, before they find us out.
기다리고 있었다.
I was waiting for you.
넌 도쿠간류! 발각된 이상 어쩔 수 없소! 각오하시오!
You're Dokuganryu! Since you found out, it can't be helped-dasu! Prepare yourself-dasu!
일단 잠깐. 난 너희들하고 싸울 생각은 없다.
Woah, slow down. I'm not intending to fight you.
자, 이 쪽으로. 육도마왕 노부나가 님이 기다리고 계신다.
This way, please. Lord Nobunaga the Rikudomaoh is waiting.
뭣이, 노부나가가?
What? Nobunaga?
이거 위험한데. 함정일 게 뻔해.
This isn't good. This has to be a trap.
어떻게 하시겠습니까, 코지로 님.
What are we going to do, Mr. Kojirō?
가 볼 수밖에 없겠군요.
I guess we'll have to go.
잘도 이 바벨 13에 잠입했구나. 칭찬해 주지.
I'll praise you, for managing to get into this Babel 13.
칭찬 안 해줘도 좋소! 대체 어쩔 생각이오!
We don't need appraisal-dasu! What are you going to do-dasu!?
흥. 나는 너희 그 완고함이 마음에 든다. 어떠냐, 내 부하가 되는 게.
Hmph. I like your stubbornness. Wouldn't you like to become my subordinates?
뭐라?
What?
흥! 웃기는 것도 작작 하시오! 나는 정의의 카라쿠리 무예가이오! 악당의 동료 따위는 안 되오!
Hmph! Don't fool around too much-dasu!
I am a Karakuri martial artist of justice-dasu! I won't become villains' friend-dasu!
위세가 좋구나, 무사시. 그럼 하나 물어 보겠다. 네게 정의란 무엇이냐.
You have might, Musashi. Then let me ask you: what is justice?
평화로운 세상을 지키는 것이오!
Protecting the peaceful world-dasu!
평화? 지금 이 세계가 평화롭다는 거냐?
Peaceful? Are you saying that the world of now is peaceful?
이에야스 아래에서 겉보기에는 평화로운 것 같아 보이지만, 지방의 호족들은 영토를 넓히기 위해 매일 전투를 하고 있지 않은가.
Under Ieyasu, it looks like it's peaceful at first sight,
but aren't powerful families in various areas are fighting to expand their territories?
평화롭게 사는 건 일부뿐으로, 수많은 타인들은 오늘 저녁도 굶으며 살고 있지 않은가.
Only a small number of people live peacefully, while others can't even have dinner tonight.
말하고 보니 그렇소...
Now you've said that, that's true-dasu...
나는 이 세상을 모조리 멸망시켜, 전쟁이란 아예 없는 새로운 세계를 만들고자 한다.
I look to lead this whole world into destruction, and create a world without any wars.
그걸 위해서는 너희같은 어린 힘이 더욱 필요하다.
For that, I need the power of young people, like you..
어떠냐. 그래도 아직 내게 힘을 빌려주지 않겠다는 것이냐.
What do you think? Wouldn't you want to lend me your powers to me?
네! 나, 노부나가 씨에게 힘을 빌려주오!
Yes! I will help Mr. Nobunaga-dasu!
바보야! 노부나가가 말하는 걸 믿으면 안 돼!
You idiot! Don't believe what Nobunaga is saying!
왜이오! 노부나가 씨가 말하는 것은 올바르지 않은 것이오?
Why-dasu? Isn't what Mr. Nobunaga saying correct-dasu?
옳다고 생각한다면, 왜 삼종의 신기를 훔치고 하는 것입니까.
If you think he's right, then why would he be trying to steal the Three Sacred Treasures?
음, 그것도 그렇소...
That makes sense, too-dasu...
분명 이 세상은 지금도 전투가 계속되고 있지만, 이에야스 님은 조금씩 전투를 없애고자 하고 계신다.
You are right in that the battles are going on even now, but Lord Ieyasu is trying to decrease the number of them.
너같이 평화롭게 살고 있는 사람들도 전부 멸하고자 하는 것은 잘못된 생각이다!
Your way of thinking, to annihilate people who're living peacefully, is wrong!
쥬베 씨에게 찬성!
I agree to Mr. Jube!
흥. 애초에 너희같은 자들은 내 위대함을 알 수 없다.
Hmph. You guys cannot understand my greatness at the first place.
한조! 이 놈들을 몰살시켜라.
Hanzo! Annihilate them.
예!
Yessir!
멈추시오!
Stop-dasu!
저런!
Nope!
한조! 비키시오!
Hanzo! Get out of my way-dasu!
흥. 노부나가 님의 권유를 거절하다니 멍청한 놈들이군.
Hmph. Refusing Lord Nobunaga's invitation? How foolish.
처음부터 그랬으면 좋았을 것을 거드름피우기는!
You should have done that at the first place. You're just putting on airs!
처치해라!
Get them!
송사리가 상대가 될까보냐!
You think those small fries can be my enemies?
건방지다! 조조 아머!
How impudent! Sousou Armor!
나도이오!
Me too-dasu!
카라쿠리 변화! 겐토쿠 아머!
Karakuri Shift! Gentoku Armor!
한조! 각오!
Hanzo! Prepare yourself!
카라쿠리 변화! 칸우 아머!
Karakuri Shift! Kanu Armor!
한조! 이번엔 못 달아날 것이오!
Hanzo! You're not getting away this time-dasu!
멍청한 놈. 여기가 어디라 생각하냐!
You fool. Where do you think you are?
뭐야?
What's this?
걸려들었구나!
You fell into my trap!
어쩔 생각이오, 한조!
What are you going to do-dasu, Hanzo!?
이걸로 우릴 생포할 셈이냐!
Are you going to take us prisoners!?
흥. 살려둘 생각따위 없다.
Hmph. I wasn't even thinking of letting you alive.
수공!
Inundation!
여기까지 헤엄쳐 온 너희들이라면 분명 수영하는 게 특기겠지. 여기서 죽기 전가지 실컷 수영이나 해 보아라.
I'm guessing your specialty is swimming, since you swam your way to here. Swim all as you wanted, before you die.
젠장! 익사체로 끝장날 생각 없소!
Damn! We're not going to end up drowning-dasu!
갑주가!
My armor!
육도마왕 노부나가를 눈 앞에 두고, 어항 속에서 익사체가 되는가, 무사시! 질풍노도의 반격을 기다려라!
Right before confronting Nobunaga the Rikudomaoh,
will you end up becoming a drowned body in some fishbowl, Musashi!? Wait for the stormy counterattack!
싸우고 맞았어
I fought and I got beaten
코피 쓩이야 랑데부
Nosebleed drips rendezvous
나도 지지 않으려 한발!
I can't lose, so take my blow!
핀치 펀치로 대역전
Pinch! Punch! I won by reversal
다음 시간 즐거운
Next is delightful lunchtime
급식일 텐데
But it's not delightful today
선생님의 벼락이
The thunder of my teacher
나한테만 떨어져 왔어
only hit me and nobody else
사정을 말해도
I tried to explain
들어주지 않는 채
But he won't listen
어떻게 해도 역시
Now whatever I do
눈물이 나오고 말아
I end up crying
울면서 밥먹으면
Don't cry when you eat, or
완전 맛없어
it tastes totally bad
울면서 밥먹으면
Don't cry when you eat, or
완전 맛없어
it tastes totally bad
울면서 밥먹으면
Don't cry when you eat, or
완전 맛없어
it tastes totally bad
울면서 밥먹으면
Don't cry when you eat, or
왠지 안타까워
you'll feel downhearted
잡히고 만 우리. 노부나가 놈은 죽여도 상관없으니 센히메를 데리고 오라고 도쿠간류에게 명령했소.
We got caught. Meanwhile, that Nobunaga bastard ordered Dokuganryu to capture Senhime, no matter her life-dasu.
큰일이오! 오츠루도 살해당할지도 모르오!
This is bad-dasu! Otsuru might be killed, too-dasu!
그런데 거기에 모두가 급히 달려왔소!
But at there, everyone came to help-dasu!
우시와카, 벤케이, 제니가탄 두목이오.
Ushiwaka, Benkei, and Boss Zenigatan-dasu.
다음 이야기! 바벨 13을 파괴하라 이오
Next story! Destroy Babel 13
질풍노도의 쌍룡검이오!
It's the stormy Double Dragon Sword-dasu!
다음 이야기
바벨 13을
부수어라 이오
기대하세요!
Next Episode
Destroy
Babel 13
Look forwards for it!